blognife.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Blognife

  * ## Privacy Policy:

Essencz Solutions (" **Essencz Solutions** ") operates Blognife.com and may operate other websites. It is Essencz Solutions policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Essencz Solutions collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Essencz Solutions purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Essencz Solutions visitors use its website. From time to time, Essencz Solutions may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Essencz Solutions also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on Blognife.com blogs/sites. Essencz Solutions only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Essencz Solutions websites choose to interact with Essencz Solutions in ways that require Essencz Solutions to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Essencz Solutions gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at [Blognife.com](http://blognife.com/) to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Essencz Solutions are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Essencz Solutions collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Essencz Solutions. Essencz Solutions does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

Essencz Solutions may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Essencz Solutions may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Essencz Solutions does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Essencz Solutions discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Essencz Solutions behalf or to provide services available at Essencz Solutions websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Essencz Solutions websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Essencz Solutions will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Essencz Solutions discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Essencz Solutions believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Essencz Solutions, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Essencz Solutions website and have supplied your email address, Essencz Solutions may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Essencz Solutions and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Essencz Solutions takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Essencz Solutions uses cookies to help Essencz Solutions identify and track visitors, their usage of Essencz Solutions website, and their website access preferences. Essencz Solutions visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Essencz Solutions websites, with the drawback that certain features of Essencz Solutions websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If Essencz Solutions, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Essencz Solutions goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Essencz Solutions may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Essencz Solutions and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Essencz Solutions may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Essencz Solutions sole discretion. Essencz Solutions encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a Blognife.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
